I am pregnant with my first child and my mom had decided to tell me the full story of my
birth and how I could have possibly died, thinking back on it.
This is all from my parents' perspective, obviously, since I was just being born.
When my mom found out she was pregnant with me, my grandma insisted she go to this doctor
because he was so amazing and really nice and knows what H is doing.
Well, my mom went to him and right away she knew there was something not right about him,
but kept going to him upon my grandma's insistence.
Well, my mom developed gallbladder disease and had a lot of trouble with it since they
couldn't properly treat it with me being present in my mom's body.
So she had to eat a special diet and try John through the pregnancy as best she could.
When she got to her TH week appointment, she voiced how she couldn't wait until I was born
so her misery with the gallbladder can end by having it removed.
My dad and mom agree that the doctor, while obviously high on something, decided then
and there to have my mom induced.
He didn't tell her what he was doing until it was already happening.
She asked him why, worried it was something to do with me.
Nope, he just decided that since she voiced she couldn't wait, he would just induce her
since she was far enough along.
So, I was born weeks early and developed jaundice, which was quickly cured by sunshine, thank
god it was May.
Thankfully, that was all my parents needed to worry about me health-wise.
The doctor was arrested about a week after I was born, we think, due to him stealing
drugs from the hospital.
This was probably the last time my mom took advice from my grandma when it came to important
decisions like this.
I dk if this counts as a really crazy story, but thanks if you read it.